Guide to the Board of Trustees Records, 1860-ongoing UA.02.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Board of Trustees records
1860-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.). Board of Trustees
Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.). Board of Trustees
Duke University. Board of Trustees
UA.02.01.0001
130 Linear Feet
The Duke University Board of Trustees has existed since 1924, and grew out of the Trinity College Board of Trustees that existed from 1859 to 1924. The Board is responsible for making major steering decisions in the administration of the school. The Board of Trustees records contain minutes, agendas, correspondence, reports, subject files, trustee handbooks, and other records of the Board and Executive, standing, and ad hoc committees. The minutes include reports, correspondence, resolutions, recommendations for the conferring of degrees, for employment and renewal of employment, and other material. Reports include those made by University officers, Board committees, and outside consultants. The Board's records also include statements of funds and scholarships, investment reports, correspondence, audits, bylaws, petitions from students, and other material. English.
Access Restrictions
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
Provenance
The Board of Trustees Records were received by the University Archives as transfers from 1974-2012.
Historical Note
The Board of Trustees of Duke University was originally formed when the Union Institute Society's 1839 constitution established a body with responsibility for the oversight of the affairs of Union Institute Academy of Randolph County, North Carolina. The Board was legally recognized in 1841 by an act of the North Carolina General Assembly incorporating Union Institute Academy as a private school for boys. In 1851, the Union Institute Academy changed to become Normal College, an institution dedicated to the training of teachers. The Board members remained largely the same, but new members were also added. In 1856, the Board approved resolutions to allow Normal College to become the official college of the North Carolina Conference of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. With the change came more Board members representing the Methodist Church, and a new charter was approved by the Board. In 1859, Normal College changed its name to "Trinity College." A set of bylaws was also drawn up, and these by-laws form the basis of Duke University's present-day bylaws.
In 1892, Trinity College moved to Durham County to take advantage of a more urban setting and to seek more financial support. In 1924, the University received a major endowment from James B. Duke, who along with his father, Washington Duke, and brother, Benjamin Duke, had made a fortune in tobacco and power companies. In his honor, the Board of Trustees changed the name of Trinity College to Duke University (although the undergraduate institution still retains the name Trinity College).
Although the bylaws of the Board have been modified over the years, the Duke University Board of Trustees is still the body that makes the university's major administrative and strategic decisions. The Board consists of 36 members, including the current president of Duke University. As of 2005, the Bylaws of Duke University stated, "The thirty-six elected Trustees shall be elected as follows: twelve by the North Carolina Conference of the United Methodist Church; twelve by the Western North Carolina Conference of the United Methodist Church; and twelve by the graduates of Duke University." The Board is administered by the Office of the University Secretary. To read the current bylaws of Duke University and to see a list of current Board members, visit the University Secretary's webpage at: http://www.duke.edu/web/ous/
Collection Overview
The Board of Trustees records contain minutes, agendas, correspondence, reports, subject files, trustee handbooks, and other records of the Board and Executive, standing, and ad hoc committees. The minutes include reports, correspondence, resolutions, recommendations for the conferring of degrees, for employment and renewal of employment, and other material. Reports include those made by University officers, Board committees, and outside consultants. The Board's records also include statements of funds and scholarships, investment reports, correspondence, audits, bylaws, petitions from students, and other material. The minute book covering June 1901-June 1910 was destroyed by fire in 1911, but some handwritten minutes for the period were preserved and have been typed out. There are gaps in the minutes for the period 1925-1930.
The collection is divided into three main sections: Trinity College, Duke University, and Duke University Unprocessed Materials. The Trinity College series begins in 1860 and ends in 1924, the year Trinity College became Duke University. There are minute books, topical files, and yearly files. Because a fire destroyed the minute book covering June 1901-June 1910, some handwritten minutes have been transcribed; these can be found in the yearly files.
The second series, Duke University, covers 1924 to the present. It includes minutes of the Board and the Executive Committee, general records of the Board and the Executive Committee, reports, financial records, committees, and unprocessed materials. All materials less than 50 years old are closed except by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
The third series, Duke University Unprocessed Materials, consists primarily of materials less than fifty years old, and so are restricted except by permission from the Board of Trustees.
Related Material
Board of Trustees Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Office of the University Secretary Records
Duke University Archives
Nancy Hanks Trustee Records
Duke University Archives
Mary Duke Biddle Trent Semans Board of Trustees and Duke University Records
Duke University Archives
Charles B. Wade Records
Duke University Archives
Bunyan S. Womble Papers
Duke University Archives
Willis Smith Papers
Duke University Rare Books, Manuscripts, and Special Collections Department
Photographs
Duke University Archives
Oversized Photographs
Duke University Archives
Other Guides to the Board of Trustees Records
The University Archives has compiled an inventory of the items dated from 1901-1925.
The University Archives has compiled a personal name index for the minutes of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, circa 1946-1978.
The University Archives has compiled a subject index of the minutes of the Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, circa 1946-1978.
Conditions Governing Access
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Bibliography
Nora C. Chaffin Trinity College, 1839-1892: The Beginnings of Duke University, Durham, N.C.: Duke University Press, 1950
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.). Board of Trustees; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- Faculty; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- Administration; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Finance; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Faculty; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Students; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- History; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- History; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- Finance; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.) -- Students; Trinity College (Randolph County, N.C.). Board of Trustees; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Administration; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Finance; Duke University -- History; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Faculty
- Trinity College, 1860-1948
  Scope and Contents note
  Trinity College was the forerunner of Duke University, and existed from 1859 to 1924. The Trinity College series includes minutes, topical files, yearly files, and Building Committee files.
  - Minutes, 1860-1922
    The minutes of Trinity College have been bound into volumes. The volume that covered the dates after February 1900 and before June 1911 for the Board of Trustees was destroyed by fire. Some information about the meetings held during these years can be found in the yearly files. The minutes are arranged chronologically, and Board of Trustees minutes are followed by Executive Committee minutes. The volumns within Box 1 were removed and boxed individually. The folders were added to Box 2. As such, Box 1 no longer exists (as of December 2012).
    - Minutes, 1860 June 19-1879 June 12 (Volume 1)
    - Minutes, 1880 June 9-1891 June 10 (Volume 2)
    - Minutes, 1891 Sept. 19-1900 Feb. 19 (Volume 3)
    - Photocopy of minutes of 1889 Dec. 4, 1890 March 20 (Box 2)
      These minutes represent the beginning of the Duke family's involvement.
    - Minutes, 1860 June 19-1879 June 12 (loose material removed from bound volume) (Box 2)
    - Volume, June 5, 1911-November 4, 1922 (Box 2)
    - Stenographer's Notebook, June 1911-June 1922 (Box 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1887-1923
    - Volume, 1887-1889 (Box 3)
    - Volume, August 1892-November 1892 (Box 3)
      Volume also includes minutes and reports of faculty meetings.
    - Volume, April 22, 1893-April 27, 1901 (Box 3)
    - 2 volumes, June 10, 1901-May 1, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Topics, 1888-1948
    The Topics files are arranged alphabetically. Note that some of the contents of the file "Trustee Lists" overlap with the establishment of Duke University.
    - Clipping, Raleigh Christian Advocate, March 26, 1890 (Box 5)
    - Contracts, 1891-1894 (Box 5)
    - Documents on moving from Randolph County to Durham, 1889-1892 (Box 5)
    - Financial Records and Reports of the Treasurer and Financial Secretary, 1888-1891 (Box 5)
    - "The History of Trinity College," circa 1915-1916 (Box 5)
    - Letterbook, Board of Trustees Chair, 1897-1902 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1889-1894 (Box 5)
    - Petitions, 1888-1891 (Box 5)
    - Plan of Dr. Few for Bible Department, undated (Box 5)
    - Pledges by Durham Citizens, 1890 (Box 5)
      These were monetary pledges to the Board of Trustees made by Durham citizens in an effort to get Trinity College to move to Durham instead of Raleigh.
    - Trustee Lists, 1888-1948 (Box 5)
      Includes chronologically arranged lists followed by summary lists.
  - Yearly Files, 1901-1924
    These yearly files include correspondence, handwritten and transcribed minutes, financial information, President's Reports, Treasurer's Reports, Headmaster's Reports, and other materials. Sometimes financial statements or other groups of materials were separated within a year; these materials are still organized chronologically, but placed after the general yearly file.
    - 1901 (Box 5)
    - 1902 (Box 5)
    - 1903 (Box 5)
    - 1904 (Box 5)
    - 1905 (Box 5)
    - 1906 (Box 5)
    - 1907 (Box 5)
    - 1908 (Box 5)
    - 1909 (Box 5)
    - 1910 (Box 5)
    - 1911 (Box 5)
    - 1912 (Box 5)
    - 1913 (Box 5)
    - 1913 - Financial Statement (Box 5)
    - 1914 (Box 5)
    - 1914 - Financial Statement (Box 5)
    - 1915 (Box 5)
    - 1915 - Athletic Council Business (Box 5)
    - 1915 - Financial Statement and Treasurer's Report (Box 5)
    - 1916 (Box 5)
    - 1916 - Financial Statement (Box 5)
    - 1917 (Box 5)
    - 1917 - Financial Statement (Box 5)
    - 1917 - Treasurer's Report and Trinity Park School Treasurer's Report (Box 5)
    - 1918 (Box 5)
    - 1918 - Financial Statement (Box 5)
    - 1918 - Football Petitions (Box 5)
    - 1918 - Treasurer's Report (Box 5)
    - 1919 (Box 5)
    - 1919 - Financial Statement (Box 6)
    - 1919 - Randolph County Property (Box 6)
    - 1920 (Box 6)
    - 1920 - Financial Statement (Box 6)
    - 1921 (Box 6)
    - 1921 - Financial Statement (Box 6)
    - 1922 (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - 1922 - Financial Statement (Box 6)
    - 1923 (Box 6)
    - 1924 (Box 6)
    - 1924 - Executive Committee (Box 6)
  - Building Committee, 1890-1893 (Box 7)
    The Building Committee helped plan Trinity College's move from Randolph County to Durham County.
    - Minutes Book, 1890 (Box 7)
      This book also contains student grades dating 1893 to 1906.
    - Records, 1890-1893 (Box 7)
- Duke University, 1923-2010
  The Duke University series contains materials generated after Trinity College officially became Duke University in December 1924. The series is organized into several subseries: Meeting Minutes, Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Board of Trustees General Records, Executive Committee General Records, Committees, Reports, Financial Records, and Unprocessed Materials. All materials less than 50 years old are closed except by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
  - Meeting Minutes, 1923-1985
    The minutes of the Board of Trustees have been bound into volumes for ease of use. These volumes contain the officially recorded minutes of the Board. For supplementary materials, see the Board of Trustees General Records subseries.
    - June 4, 1923-June 4, 1933 (Volume 1)
    - February 28, 1934-May 22, 1943 (Volume 2)
    - January 29, 1944-December 10, 1949 (Volume 3)
    - June 3, 1950-May 30, 1953 (Volume 4)
    - February 24, 1954-June 2, 1956 (Volume 5)
    - February 27, 1957-May 31, 1958 (Volume 6)
    - February 25, 1959-June 4, 1960 (Volume 7)
    - March 8, 1961-June 2, 1962 (Volume 8)
    - November 2, 1962-May 30, 1964 (Volume 9)
    - November 6, 1964-June 4, 1966 (Volume 10)
    - November 4, 1966-June 3, 1967 (Volume 11)
    - December 9, 1967-June 1, 1968 (Volume 12)
    - December 7, 1968-May 31, 1969 (Volume 13)
    - December 13, 1969-September 9, 1970 (Volume 14)
    - October 8, 1970-June 5, 1971 (Volume 15)
    - December 11, 1971-May 13, 1972 (Volume 16)
    - December 8, 1972-May 12, 1973 (Volume 17)
    - September 21, 1973-May 11, 1974 (Volume 18)
    - September 28, 1974-May 10, 1975 (Volume 19)
    - September 26, 1975-December 13, 1975 (Volume 20)
    - March 5, 1976-May 8, 1976 (Volume 21)
    - September 24, 1976-December 11, 1976 (Volume 22)
    - February 25, 1977-May 7, 1977 (Volume 23)
    - September 23, 1977-December 10, 1977 (Volume 24)
    - February 24, 1978-May 6, 1978 (Volume 25)
    - September 29, 1978-December 9, 1978 (Volume 26)
    - February 23, 1979-May 5, 1979 (Volume 27)
    - September 28, 1979-December 8, 1979 (Volume 28)
    - February 22, 1980-May 10, 1980 (Volume 29)
    - September 26, 1980-December 13, 1980 (Volume 30)
    - February 27, 1981-May 9, 1981 (Volume 31)
    - September 25, 1981-December 12, 1981 (Volume 32)
    - February 26, 1982-May 8, 1982 (Volume 33)
    - September 24, 1982-December 11, 1982 (Volume 34)
    - February 25, 1983-May 7, 1983 (Volume 35)
    - September 23, 1983-December 10, 1983 (Volume 36)
    - March 2, 1984-May 5, 1984 (Volume 37)
    - September 28, 1984-December 8, 1984 (Volume 38)
    - March 1, 1985-May 4, 1985 (Volume 39)
    - September 27, 1985-December 7, 1985 (Volume 40)
    - February 28, 1986-May 3, 1986 (Volume 41)
    - September 26, 1986-December 13, 1986 (Volume 42)
    - February 27, 1987-May 9, 1987 (Volume 43)
    - September 25, 1987-December 12, 1987 (Volume 44)
    - February 26, 1988-May 7, 1988 (Volume 45)
    - September 23, 1988-December 10, 1988 (Volume 46)
    - February 24, 1989-May 13, 1989 (Volume 47)
    - September 29, 1989-December 9, 1989 (Volume 48)
    - February 23-24, 1990 (Volume 49)
    - May 11, 1990 (Volume 50)
    - October 5, 1990 (Volume 51)
    - December 7, 1990 (Volume 52)
    - February 22, 1991 (Volume 53)
    - May 10, 1991 (Volume 54)
    - September 27, 1991 (Volume 55)
    - December 6, 1991 (Volume 56)
    - December 6, 1991 (Volume 57)
    - February 28, 1992 (Volume 58)
    - May 15, 1992 (Volume 59)
    - September 25-26, 1992 (Volume 60)
    - December 10, 1992 (Volume 61)
    - February 26-27, 1993 (Volume 62)
    - May 14-15, 1993 (Volume 63)
    - October 1-2, 1993 (Volume 64)
    - December 10-11, 1993 (Volume 65)
    - December 10-11, 1993 (Volume 66)
    - February 25-26, 1994 (Volume 67)
    - May 6-7, 1994 (Volume 68)
    - September 30-October 1, 1994 (Volume 69)
    - December 9-10, 1994 (Volume 70)
    - February 24-25, 1995 (Volume 71)
    - May 12-13, 1995 (Volume 72)
    - September 29-30, 1995 (Volume 73)
    - December 8-9, 1995 (Volume 74)
    - February 23, 1996 (Volume 75)
    - May 10-11, 1996 (Volume 76)
    - September 27-28, 1996 (Volume 77)
    - December 13-14, 1996 (Volume 78)
    - February 28-March 1, 1997 (Volume 79)
    - May 16-17, 1997 (Volume 80)
    - September 26-27, 1997 (Volume 81)
    - December 5-6, 1997 (Volume 82)
    - February 27, 1998 (Volume 83)
    - May 15-16, 1998 (Volume 84)
    - October 2-3, 1998 (Volume 85)
    - December 4-5, 1998 (Volume 86)
    - February 26-27, 1999 (Volume 87)
    - May 14-15, 1999 (Volume 88)
    - October 1-2, 1999 (Volume 89)
    - December 3-4, 1999 (Volume 90)
    - February 25-26, 2000 (Volume 91)
    - May 12-13, 2000 (Volume 92)
    - October 6-7, 2000 (Volume 93)
    - December 1, 2000 (Volume 94)
    - February 23-24, 2001 (Volume 95)
    - May 11-12, 2001 (Volume 96)
    - October 5-6, 2001 (Volume 97)
    - December 7-8, 2001 (Volume 98)
    - February 22-23, 2002 (Volume 99)
    - May 10-11, 2002 (Volume 100)
    - October 4-5, 2002 (Volume 101)
    - December 6, 2002 (Volume 102)
    - February 28, 2003 (Volume 103)
    - May 9-10, 2003 (Volume 104)
    - October 3-4, 2003 (Volume 105)
    - December 5-6, 2003 and December 11, 2003 (Volume 106)
    - February 27-28, 2004 (Volume 107)
    - May 7-8, 2004 (Volume 108)
    - October 1-2, 2004 (Volume 109)
    - December 3-4, 2004 (Volume 110)
    - February 25-26, 2005 (Volume 111)
    - May 13-14, 2005 (Volume 112)
    - September 30-October 1, 2005 (Volume 113)
    - December 2-3, 2005 (Volume 114)
    - February 24-25, 2006 (Volume 115)
    - May 12-13, 2006 (Volume 116 (part 1))
    - September 29-30, 2006 (Volume 116 (part 2))
    - December 1-2, 2006 (Volume 117)
    - There is no volume 118. (Volume 118)
    - February 23-24, 2007 (Volume 119)
    - May 11-12, 2007 (Volume 120)
    - September 28-29, 2007 (Volume 121)
    - December 7-8, 2007 (Volume 122)
    - February 28-March 1, 2008 (Volume 123)
    - May 9-10, 2008 (Volume 124)
    - October 3-4, 2008 (Volume 125)
    - December 5-6, 2008 (Volume 126)
    - February 27-28, 2009 (Volume 127)
    - May 8-9, 2009 (Volume 128)
    - October 2-3, 2009 (Volume 129)
    - December 4-5, 2009 (Volume 130)
    - February 26-27, 2010 (Volume 131)
    - May 14-15, 2010 (Volume 132)
    - October 1-2, 2010 (Volume 133)
    - December 3-4, 2010 (Volume 134)
    - Duplicate Minutes, 1946-1979
      These minutes were received from the Duke Endowment (A91-57) and duplicate the contents of some of the volumes above.
      - May 24, 1946-December 7, 1968 (Box 16)
      - March 7, 1969-December 9, 1972 (Box 16)
      - March 1, 1973-September 28, 1974 (Box 16)
      - March 7, 1975-December 11, 1976 (Box 16)
      - February 25, 1977-February 24, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Meeting minutes, electronic copies, 1980-2019 (Digital-materials UA02010001-SET-0001)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1923-1985
    The minutes of the Executive Committee have been bound into volumes for ease of use. These volumes contain the officially recorded minutes of the Executive Committee. For supplementary materials, see the Executive Committee General Records subseries.
    - July 25, 1923-May 6, 1933 (Volume 1)
    - September 8, 1933-June 30, 1943 (Volume 2)
    - September 29, 1943-December 10, 1949 (Volume 3)
    - January 25, 1950-December 1, 1954 (Volume 4)
    - February 23, 1955-November 26, 1958 (Volume 5)
    - February 24, 1959-November 30, 1960 (Volume 6)
    - January 3, 1961-June 1, 1962 (Volume 7)
    - September 26, 1962-May 29, 1964 (Volume 8)
    - September 26, 1964-June 4, 1965 (Volume 9)
    - July 2, 1965-June 3, 1966 (Volume 10)
    - August 1, 1966-March 2, 1967 (Volume 11)
    - April 6, 1966-June 2, 1967 (Volume 12)
    - July 14, 1967-October 8, 1967 (Volume 13)
    - November 10, 1967-January 12, 1968 (Volume 14)
    - February 9, 1968-April 5, 1968 (Volume 15)
    - April 10, 1968-May 31, 1968 (Volume 16)
    - July 12, 1968-September 27, 1968 (Volume 17)
    - November 1, 1968-January 17, 1969 (Volume 18)
    - March 6, 1969-March 28, 1969 (Volume 19)
    - May 2, 1969-May 31, 1969 (Volume 20)
    - July 11, 1969-October 3, 1969 (Volume 21)
    - November 7, 1969-January 16, 1970 (Volume 22)
    - March 5, 1970-May 29, 1970 (Volume 23)
    - July 10, 1970-November 6, 1970 (Volume 24)
    - December 11, 1970-April 2, 1971 (Volume 25)
    - April 30, 1971-June 4, 1971 (Volume 26)
    - July 16, 1971-October 1, 1971 (Volume 27)
    - November 5, 1971-January 14, 1972 (Volume 28)
    - March 2, 1972-June 9, 1972 (Volume 29)
    - August 25, 1972-September 29, 1972 (Volume 30)
    - November 3, 1972-January 19, 1973 (Volume 31)
    - March 1, 1973-June 15, 1973 (Volume 32)
    - July 20, 1973-November 2, 1973 (Volume 33)
    - December 7, 1973-January 18, 1974 (Volume 34)
    - February 28, 1974-June 14, 1974 (Volume 35)
    - August 23, 1974-December 6, 1974 (Volume 36)
    - January 17, 1975-June 13, 1975 (Volume 37)
    - July 18, 1975-November 7, 1975 (Volume 38)
    - January 16, 1976-June 11, 1976 (Volume 39)
    - July 16, 1976-November 5, 1976 (Volume 40)
    - January 14, 1977-June 10, 1977 (Volume 41)
    - July 15, 1977-November 4, 1977 (Volume 42)
    - January 13, 1978-June 29, 1978 (Volume 43)
    - July 15, 1978-June 21, 1979 (Volume 44)
    - July 11, 1979-June 13, 1980 (Volume 45)
    - July 18, 1980-June 30, 1981 (Volume 46)
    - July 17, 1981-May 2, 1982 (Volume 47)
    - July 16, 1982-June 10, 1983 (Volume 48)
    - November 4, 1983-June 15, 1984 (Volume 49)
    - November 2, 1984-June 14, 1985 (Volume 50)
    - August 23, 1985-June 13, 1986 (Volume 51)
    - August 22, 1986-June 12, 1987 (Volume 52)
    - August 21, 1987-June 10, 1988 (Volume 53)
    - August 19, 1988-June 10, 1988 (Volume 54)
    - August 25, 1989-June 15, 1990 (Volume 55)
    - July 10, 1990-April 5, 1991 (Volume 56)
    - June 14, 1991-April 3, 1992 (Volume 57)
    - June 12, 1992-June 11, 1993 (Volume 58)
    - July 12, 1993-January 14, 1994 (Volume 59)
    - April 8, 1994-June 10, 1994 (Volume 60)
    - July 27, 1994-August 19, 1994 (Volume 61)
    - November 4, 1994-January 13, 1995 (Volume 62)
    - April 7, 1995-June 9, 1995 (Volume 63)
    - August 18, 1995-June 14, 1996 (Volume 64)
    - August 23, 1996-June 13, 1997 (Volume 65)
    - August 22, 1997-January 16, 1998 (Volume 66)
    - April 3, 1998-June 19, 1998 (Volume 67)
    - August 21, 1998-February 25 and 27, 1999 (Volume 68)
    - April 9, 1999-June 11, 1999 (Volume 69)
    - August 20, 1999-June 16, 2000 (Volume 70)
    - July 21, 2000-December 6, 2000 (Volume 71)
    - April 6, 2001-June 16, 2001 (Volume 72)
    - August 21, 2001-June 14, 2002 (Volume 73)
    - August 23, 2002-June 20, 2003 (Volume 74)
    - August 29, 2003 (Volume 75)